nativecos.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy | Native Deodorant

Native Cos. is a Delaware company incorporated as Zenlen, Inc. (hereinafter, “Native”, “Native”, “we”, or “us”). Native wants you to know what information we learn about you when you visit our website ([www.nativecos.com](https://www.nativecos.com/), or any link affiliated thereto, the “Site”), what we do with that information, and any other information you voluntarily provide us through this Site or by other means and how you can view or change the information we have. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes our information collection and use practices on this Site. It does not apply to information you might provide on another site operated by us, or one of our partners or affiliates, nor does it apply to information you may provide to us through other forums, including offline or through electronic mail. By accessing or using the Site, you are consenting to the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, you should leave the Site immediately.

**Internet-Related Information Gathered Passively**

We collect information from visitors to our Site, including the referring URL, your demographic information, your IP address, which browser you used to come to the Site, the country, state or province, the pages of our Site that you viewed during your visit and any search terms entered on our Site, for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, and to monitor the level of activity on our Site. We track visitors’ traffic patterns throughout their online sessions, including pages or specific URLs a visitor views while using the Site. We use your information to diagnose problems with our servers and software and to administer our Site. We may share any information that we collect on our Site and demographic information with third-parties, to the extent we determine beneficial to your experience or our business.

**Actively Collected Personal Information You Provide**

If you provide information about yourself by registering on a page, filling out a survey, subscribing to our mailing list or otherwise voluntarily telling us about yourself or your activities, we will collect and use that information to respond to your request, and for any other purpose, including identifying user preferences and improving our services and the content of this Site.

**Sharing Information**

We may share your information with affiliates with whom we have joint marketing arrangements or with other third parties. If you do not want us to share your information with our marketing affiliates, then please let us know by contacting us at [support@nativecos.com](mailto:support@nativecos.com).

We employ companies to perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, processing credit cards, delivering packages, and services related to the design, maintenance and improvement of this Site and our database and related systems. These companies may have access to certain information that you have provided to us.

We may use the services of third parties to collect and use information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services.

**Links To Other Websites**

We may provide, as a convenience to you, links from our Site to other websites, including sites operated by us, our partners, associates, or independent third parties. Each website has its own privacy policies and practices, as described on such site. Those policies and practices may be different than the policies and practices described herein, and we urge you to read such site’s privacy policy carefully before you use or submit information to that site. Additionally, to the extent that you follow a link to a website operated by an independent third party, please be aware that we exercise no authority or control over that third party, and cannot and are not responsible for any information that you may submit at that site.

**Where Do We Store And How Do We Secure Your Personal Information**

Your information will be kept in a database held on servers kept in a physically and technologically secure environment located in the United States, accessed only by authorized personnel or contractors. Any transmission of your credit card information will be encrypted.

**No Data Collected from Children**

Our Site is not directed at children under the age of 13. As a result, we will not knowingly collect information from minors in the United States with or without consent from their parents or guardians.

**Cookies**

When you visit this Site, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect information and enhance your experience online through web browsers and applications. This site may only function properly if cookies are enabled. Native uses persistent cookies to authenticate that you have visited the site before and display content that is relevant and specific to you. Cookies are very small files that store information about your visit to and use of this Site. Most major commercial internet sites use them and they make your internet-surfing more useful and less time-consuming for you because they store information that is reusable each time you visit this Site, such as preferences you have chosen to share with us. Cookies allow us to provide information that is more meaningful to you without asking you the same questions every time you visit us. You may get also cookies from our advertisers and service providers.

Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, we may not be able to provide you with as good of an experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs by utilizing the cookie and you may not be able to utilize some features of the Site.

We may also use our own cookies to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests.

**Change Policy**

We reserve the right to change or update this Policy at any time by posting a notice that we are changing our Privacy Policy or by sending an e-mail message to previously registered visitors.

**What To Do If You Have Questions Or Concerns About Your Information, Or If You Need To Contact Us**

If you need information or have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personal information, or wish to review all of your personal information, you may contact us at [support@nativecos.com](mailto:support@nativecos.com) or via mail at 225 Bush Street, Suite 1900, San Francisco, California, 94107.

This Policy is effective as of July 7, 2015.
